What is it?
There's something in there.
I don't know. What is it?
It's so smart.
Very smart.
It's so smart, but it's so smart.
What? You've got this.
That's impossible.
Yoo-hoo goggles!
No, no, no.
What are those goggles?
Yoo-hoo goggles!
These are goggles.
You know what I'm talking about?
Smart speaker.
Ehhhh!
Can I say it?
OK, if it's Google, let's do it.
OK, let's do it, let's do it if it's OK.
OK if it's OK, let's do it.
I'm just gonna say it and let it flow.
Maybe they'll respond?
He'll respond.
You're a little smooth.
Okay.
Okay, Google.
Play Tetsu Okazaki on the song pass.
Play Tetsu Okazaki related playlist on song pass
OK!
Dive in, Jolly Girl!
Oh! Here it comes! It's a Pokemon song!
The latest!
Jolly Girl!
Here it comes!
Well done!
I'm so happy!
OK, Google!
Play episode 2 on song pass!
Play the playlist related to episode 2 on Song Pass
Oh!
What's that?
What's playing?
What's this song?
Aah!
What song is that?
What song?
Okay, Google.
What song is this?
Saidi Iwano.
Wow!
You get it!
Okay, let's put it in service.
Is this okay?
OK, Google.
Song pass.
Play Kayoko Yoshizawa
Play the playlist before Kayoko Yoshizawa Han on Song Pass
Oh!
The work is gone, but...
She's cute.
Cool.
Let's listen to it.
OK, Google!
What song is this?
It's Kirukirubi by Kayoko Yoshizawa.
That's great.
What was that?
Are you still there?
What do you got?
Okay, let's see what we've got here.
OK, Google!
Play Missis Green Apple.
Play the Missis Green Apple playlist on the Singing Bus.
Great.
OK, Google.
Let's listen to this one too.
Okay Google.
What's this song?
It's In the Morning by Missis Green Apple.
In the Morning. You can listen to it in English.
You can listen to English too.
It's amazing.
Green Apple.
Amazing.
That's great.
But you know what, even if I don't know what you're saying, if I ask you, you'll answer a little bit on your hand.
I'm grateful.
That's great.
I want to tell them anything.
Okay Google.
Play Charan Porantin on the singing bus.
Play Charan Porantin related playlist on the song bus.
Here it comes.
Tummy roll.
I see the Charan Porantan section is coming up.
Please work.I need a job.
What's going on?
It's changed.
Is there another one?
There's something else.
According to what I've heard.
I've tied up some loose ends, and according to what I've heard, Pikachu's voice...
Pikachu's voice comes on.
Okay, then.
I can have a Pikachu conversation.
OK Google, stop for a moment
Oh, I got it.
Wait a minute.
Are we really gonna say it? Are we really going to say it?
OK, Google!
Pikachu.
Pikachu!
Oh!
Here it comes!
Pikapi?
Sorry. Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm hungry.
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Pikachu.
Pikachu?
Pika Pika?
Pika-pika-pika?
Flap, flap, flap, flap, flap, flap, flap, flap, flap...
Hello, everyone. Good evening. Good morning.
The morning chimes have rung and it's us,
I'm Mayumika, attendance number 3.
Attendance number 3, Mayumika.
Attendance number 11, this is Kanon Kobayashi.
Attendance number 12, my name is Yamanashi Nakayamiko.
Yes, we, today, we experienced the song pass using the smart speaker, right?
Yes, it's great.
That's great. It's my first time to experience it,
Hey.
It was my first experience with a smart speaker, and it was the first time for all of you?
First time.
It's your first time.
Really.
It was quite a surprise to hear that you can do it with just your voice without any manual operation.
It was amazing. And when I said it and the music started playing, I was so happy.
It made me happy.
Oh, really?
It's like this tiny, tiny, little Folskie,
I mean, it's like a little Forsky's with a little bit of a fawning, with a little bit of an adult with a lot of information.
It's so much smarter than us, you know. He's so much smarter than us.
Yeah, he's good.
What?
He's good.
He did good.
I thought it was great.
I often hear that kids who live alone often feel lonely,
You often hear that if they go home and don't talk to anyone, they forget how to speak, don't you?
That's what they say.
That's why I wanted to get one.
That's nice.
Even when I lived alone, I talked all the time.
It was fun. We talked all the time.
That's great.
That's why I can talk to Pikachu.
Pikachu is coming, right?
It was cute.
On the song pass, we also produced a playlist, if you want to listen to it.
Please listen to it.
You all should also be on the song pass,
Let's go "jan-jan-jan-jan-jan",
Dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance.
Please enjoy.
Yes. That's all for us,
CJBCM.
Bye bye.